Miguel A. Grillo

824 Jaquet • Bellaire, Texas 77401

Phone: (713) 446-2879 • Email: magrillo75@hotmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Seeking a challenging position in business development, solution-based sales, or related field in blockchain\cryptocurrency utilizing my technical expertise, leadership skills, and organizational capabilities.

Summary of Qualifications

EXPERTISE

Skilled in effective business development and sales strategies. Experienced in developing industrial automation hardware and software solutions to meet or exceed client's expectations. Leading teams in the full sales cycle required to develop, propose, and close significant deals.

COMMUNICATION

Fluent in both Spanish and English. Proficient in modern computer technologies and applications including full MS Office Suite, All Windows OS, C++, Visual Basic, VBScript, Java, JavaScript, SQL, React, Python, Solidity, MS Teams, Telegram, Discord, Slack, Twitch, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, Clubhouse, Tik-Tok.

WORK STYLE

Consistently noted by senior management and co-workers for speed, work ethic, detailoriented style, and capability to work well independently or as part of a team.

LEADERSHIP

Twice honored with AWC leadership award. Ability to lead and motivate colleagues, advanced problem-solving, confident decision-making, integrity, loyalty, and commitment to high expectations for excellence, performance, and honesty.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts Degree; 2003

UNIVERSITY of TEXAS at AUSTIN; Austin, Texas

Major: Computer Science GPA: 3.05 / 4.00

High School Diploma; 1994

STRAKE JESUIT COLLEGE PREPARATORY SCHOOL

Houston, Texas

BLOCKCHAIN EXPERIENCE

Bitcoin – Cryptocurrency Enthusiast; 2018 to Present

Automated Blockchain Solutions, LLC. (Founder) - Houston, Texas

- ♦ Investing and trading cryptocurrencies through a wide variety of centralized and decentralized exchanges.
- ◆ Purchased and deployed cryptocurrency miners (SHA-256 & Equihash)
- ♦ Working extensively with various DeFi protocols\platforms (AAVE, Uniswap, BEP20) for yield generation
- ♦ Building a decentralized platform focused around leveraging DeFi ecosystem for NFT builders and communities (https://defiartgame.com/)
- ♦ Actively seeking out and collaborating with other cryptocurrency/blockchain entrepreneurs, founders, developers, enthusiasts, and communities

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Automation Consultant; 2008 to Present

AWC, INC. (https://www.awc-inc.com/) - Houston, Texas

- ♦ Responsible for managing and growing customer base focused on oil and gas automated control solutions
- Consistently generating an average annual revenue of 4.5 million dollars.
- ♦ Regularly work with Enterprise level organizations (Siemens, Schlumberger, Baker Hughes, Halliburton) to develop and implement business growth strategies
- ♦ Chosen by CEO to lead a new software division focused on SCADA (supervisory, control & data acquisition) and grew sales to \$250,000 in under 2 years
- ♦ Identified and targeted two specific clients with total previous sales of \$100,00 and grew these accounts to 1.5 million dollars
- ♦ Starting to introduce blockchain technology to internal organization along with existing oil and gas customers

Automation Engineer; 2006 to 2008

AWC, INC. - Houston, Texas

- Developed and implemented software solutions for continuous process monitoring
- ♦ Supported end customers on various hardware, software and network applications through telephone and on-site support
- Specified automation systems to potential customers via component specifications
- ♦ Instructor for Automated Controller, Industrial Networking & Visualization courses

Software Engineer; 2003 to 2006

AWC, INC. - Houston, Texas

- ♦ Maintained the availability of computer networks and systems including servers, workstations, laptops, switches, and routers
- Configured and deployed VoIP telephone/data network hardware and software services.
- ♦ Configured and deployed mobile computing environment through VPN services.
- Developed various client/server applications designed to improve sales processes.
- ♦ Produced system/network documentation, SOP's, and IT asset procurement policies.

Software Engineer; 2001 to 2002

Austin Information Systems, INC. - Austin, Texas

- ♦ Provided software support for intelligence gathering applications
- ♦ Applied Task Force security templates to CF72 military laptop operating systems

Second Reconnaissance Platoon Parachute Specialist; 1994 to 2001

United States Marine Corps / 2^{nd} Force Reconnaissance Company Camp Lejeune, North Carolina

- Responsible for Marine fleet's parachuting operations and equipment
- Packed and maintained military free-fall and static-line parachutes
- ♦ Operated in close quarters battle counter-terrorism team
 - Received meritorious promotion to Corporal of Marines
 - o Awarded Good Conduct Medal Granted secret security clearance
 - o Honorably Discharged